you will be prosecutors Yes, it’s
вы будете прокурорами Да
cool
прикольно
Hello Hello, I’m from the city of
Здравствуйте Здравствуйте я из города
Khmelnitsk And you’re from Russia,
Хмельницке А вы из России
where Rostov is from I need to know I know such a
откуда Ростов надону о знаю знаю такой
city Big There’s a million million people
город Большой Там миллион миллионник
like a city yes And I’m from Syktyvkar you know
типа города да А я из Сыктывкара знаете
I know Komi Komi SSR Well it was by now
знаю Коми Коми ССР Ну было ко сейчас
Komi Republic Yes yes yes And I  from
Республика Коми Да да да А я из
Khmelnytsky you know where it is No
Хмельницкого знаете где это Нет к
unfortunately Dunaev
сожалению Дунаев
Ermolin I don’t
ермолин не
understand Dunaevtsy Yarmolintsy here
понимаю вот Дунаевцы ярмолинцы тут
Khmelnytsky here Letichev here
Хмельницкий тут летичев тут
Volochisk Okay I
Волочиск Ладно всё
know everything and you are 18 years old at least of course you have
зна а вам по 18 лет есть хоть конечно на
someone to study to become a prosecutor, what good is it for
кого учитесь на прокурору проку
you to be prosecutors Yes
проро вы будете прокурорами Да
Cool And you so wanted to go there
Прикольно А вы там так захотели пойти
interesting, well, I
интересно ну просто с детства
’ve just been interested in both jurisprudence since childhood. Well,
интересовала обеих юриспруденции Да ну
why is it that there are other lawyers there for the prosecutor,
почему именно на прокурора есть другие
for example,
там адвоката например
well, we study at the institute of the prosecutor’s office, but
ну Мы учимся в институте прокуратуры но
we’ll graduate, we can be anyone except a
мы выпустим можем быть кем угодно кроме
judge. We’ll also study. Well, you want a lawyer to become a
судьи Мы ещё поду Ну хотите адвоката на
lawyer, as if they don’t teach them in
адвоката как бы не учат учат на
law for  in order to become a
юриспруденции для того чтобы стать
lawyer you need to get a license Yes,
адвокатом нужно получить ещё лицензию Да
get an internship You need to live with a
получать практику Нужно там пожива у
lawyer there, be an assistant to a lawyer, yes,
адвоката быть помощником адвоката да ну
yes, but you want to be a prosecutor, they said,
да но вы хотите быть прокурором сказали
not a lawyer Well, I would like those And
а не адвокатом Ну мне бы хотелось те А
you, like me, want to join the Investigative Committee,
тебе как мне в следственный комитет
and why, well, whatever  such
хочется а почему вот ну что там такого
that it is prestigious to go there, good
что именно туда престижно неплохая
salary, lack of personnel in some places
зарплата недостаток в некоторых местах
So you will always have
кадров Так что у тебя всегда будет
a job But look, I just, well, I don’t
работа А вот смотрите Я просто Ну я не
know. There, I saw that you have an
знаю Там я видел что у вас там
investigative committee there. Well, they are also engaged in
следственный комитет Ну занимается и
repressions in Yes, that’s where they
репресси в Да вот там вот если вам
let you down.  Imagine you work in the
спустят вот Представьте вы работаете в
investigative committee, they let you down.
следственном комитете вам спустили
For example, you need to
Например нужно
fabricate some kind of Navalny. Yes, and
сфабриковано Навального какого-то Да и
what will you do? The
что вы будете делать этим прокуратура
prosecutor’s office is not in charge of the investigative committee. Yeah. Well, you’ll be in the prosecutor’s office And they’ll
Ну вот вы будете в прокуратуре И вам
let you down. What will you do to get something like
спустят такое Что вы будете делать чтобы
this down? You’ll have to rise to this level
такое спустили Нужно ещё до такого
And that is, you are
дослужиться А то есть вы
like ordinary people, just ordinary
Типа люди обычные просто обычные
Prosecutors are doing this and what do they
Прокуроры таким занима а чем они
do, supervising the public
занимаются надзор за общественным
order of
порядком прав
human rights. So they send you to write
человека Вот вот вас отправляют написать
that everything is fine, all human rights are respected,
что всё нормально соблюдены все права
like yes,
человека типа
well. Usually, on the contrary,
да ну Обычно наоборот
the prosecutor’s office tries to identify everything
прокуратура старается выявлять всё
bad, that is,
плохое то есть
Uh-huh But look  you are like girls,
Угу А вот смотрите вот вы как девушки
I just also have a higher
вот у меня просто тоже есть высшее
education in law. I understand a little,
образование юридическое Я немножко
look. How do you think
понимаю вот смотрите Как вы считаете
Navalny
ээ Навального
was convicted legally, you mean I want
осудили законно вы имеете в виду я хочу
you to tell them
вот чтобы вы их сказали
how this cannot be
как такое нельзя
said. That is, you really understand
высказывать То есть вы реально понимаете
that you live in the system  where you can’t say something like that
что вы живёте в системе где нельзя такое
Yes, because yes, but you go to
высказывать Да потому что да но идёте в
this system
эту систему
Well, where else to go for what kind of education
Ну а куда ещё идти под какое образование
besides legal prestige in Russia
кроме юридического престижа в России
in general we are not attracted to medicine
вообще медицина нас не привлекает
medicine to become a teacher bad salary
медицина стать учителем плохая зарплата
a huge number of personnel heavy
огромное количество кадров большая
workload philology Well, the majority
нагрузка филология Ну большинство
become teachers but also not ours  that
становится учителями но тоже не наши то
is, we chose what we like. Yes,
есть мы выбрали то что нам по душе Да
there are some problems besides
есть какие-то проблемы вме
others. Well, in general, in the legal system in
других Ну вообще в юридической системе в
Russia. Well, what can I do? It
России Ну а что поделать я правильно
turns out correctly that a talented person Yes,
получается что талантливому человеку Да
in Russia, in order to earn money, you need to
в России чтобы заработать деньги нужно
go only to this rotten system.
идти только вот в эту прогнившие систему
they said We go where
так не сказали Мы нути куда куда
we like it where we want it where our soul
нравится туда куда ты хочешь к чему душа
lies Well, guess your soul lies in a
лежит Ну так поди у вас лежит душа к
rotten system in which you are afraid to
прогнившая системы в которой вы боитесь
say whether it’s legal or illegal, we’re
сказать законно или незаконно его мы на
just studying in our first year, we’re still
первом курсе только учимся мы пока ещё
studying for 100 years already, that’s it  you’re
до учимся уже 100 лет всё Ну то есть вам
already scared, you understand that you can’t
уже страшно вы вы понимаете что нельзя
talk and you’re going there to enroll, we’re not
говорить и идёте туда поступать нам не
scared, everything’s scary, we’ve
страшно всё страшно
switched, that’s for sure, like it,
переключились це точно Поставьте лайк
write Yes, fill out the comment, that’s definitely
пишиться Да залиште коментар це точно
published, we’ll baptize the video, that’s even more
опубликовано буде окремим видео це дуже
showy,
показового
now I’ll say it’s just very, very
сейчас скажу это просто очень-очень
cool They understand how rotten
круто Они понимают насколько прогнившая
this thing is  the system they are afraid to say whether Navalny was imprisoned
Эта система они боятся сказать посадили
there is legal or illegal and they still
там законна или незаконна да и они при
go there Why Because it’s
этом идут туда Почему Потому что там
possible to make money there and it’s prestigious
возможно сорвать бабло и это престижно
yes That’s the whole Russia system, in order to
да Вот вот и вся Россия система ты чтобы
somehow get out into the people you have to be
как-то выбиться в люди должен быть Вот
This security official, prosecutors and so  then
этим силовиком прокурорами и так дальше
who will serve the system Yes,
который будет обслуживать систему Да
crush the people crush any
давить народ давить любые
signs of democracy Yes, all this is
паростки демократии Да всё
this video
это этот ролик
nay Telegram right now the VN axis
най Telegram прям зараз ось ВН
apok tse more and more respectfully YouTube is taking
апок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня
us through skarg or in your ban and I do
нас через скарг ор в твый бан и дуже
n’t show too many videos to people often don’t
багато вдео не показую людям вчасно не
show information about  Stream Tomu for this purpose,
показуе информация про стрими Тому для
we need to write a Mali operational link
того щоб ми Мали оперативний звязок
right away and while there in the
пишиться прямо зараз а пок там в
telegram okrim video schetezh Tsikava and
телеграме окрим видео ще теж цикава и
Korisna information and we are responsible for you
корисна информация и мы повинни з вами
trimati postiyny operational link
тримати постийний оперативный звязок
independantly in that chi show you about it
незалежно в того чи покаже вам про це
YouTube Glory to Ukraine write
YouTube Слава украини пиши